In this video, we're going to use our example automaton for recognizing viable
在这段视频中，我们将使用示例自动机来识别可行的
prefixes, to introduce one more idea, The idea of a valid item. To refresh your
前缀，来介绍另一个概念，有效项目的概念。要刷新您的
memory, here's where we left off last time. This is the complete
记忆，这就是我们上次讲到的地方。这是全部的
nondeterministic automaton for recognizing the viable prefixes of the example grammar
识别实例文法可行前缀的非确定自动机
[sound]. And Using the standard subset of states construction, we can build a
[声音]。并且使用状态构造的标准子集，我们可以构建
deterministic automaton that is equivalent to the non-deterministic automaton. So
与非确定自动机等价的确定自动机。所以
here's the deterministic automaton that recognizes exactly the same language. This
这是能够识别完全相同语言的确定性自动机。这
automa, this deterministic automaton notices the viable prefixes, of our
Automa，这个确定的自动机注意到我们的
example grammar. But now notice that each state is a set of items. So there's a set
示例语法。但现在请注意，每个州都是一组项目。所以有一套
of non-deterministic automaton states, in each of these states. And recall that what
不确定的自动机状态，在这些状态中的每一个。回想一下，什么
that means is that the non-deterministic automaton could be in any one of these
这意味着非确定性自动机可能在其中的任何一个中
states. And in particular, this state here is the start state because it has the item
各州。具体地说，这里的状态是开始状态，因为它有项
S prime goes to dot E. The states of this deterministic automaton are called
S的质数是点e。这个确定性自动机的状态被称为
variously cananugal collections of items or the cananugal collections of LR zero
项目的各种Cananugal集合或LR Zero的Cananugal集合
items. If you look in the dragon book it gives another way of constructing the LR
物品。如果你看一下龙书，它给出了另一种构建LR的方式
zero items than the one that I gave. Mine is somewhat simplified but I think also a
比我给的那件零件。我的稍微简化了一些，但我认为
little easier to understand if you are seeing this for the first time. Now we
如果你是第一次看到这个，那就更容易理解了。现在我们
need another definition. We'll say that a given item is valid for a viable prefix
需要另一个定义。我们会说给定的项对于可行的前缀是有效的
alpha beta. If the following is true, that beginning from the start symbol, this is
阿尔法·贝塔。如果以下条件为真，即从开始符号开始，则这是
our extra start symbol, and by a series of right-most derivation steps, we can get to
我们额外的开始符号，通过一系列最右边的派生步骤，我们可以得到
a configuration, alpha-x-omega, and then in one step, x can go to beta-gamma. And,
一个构型，α-x-ω，然后在一个步骤中，x可以变成β-γ。和,
what this says is after parsing alpha and beta, after seeing. Alpha and beta on the
这里说的是在解析了alpha和beta之后，在看到。Alpha和Beta在
stack, the valid items are the possible tops of the stack of items. That, that we
堆栈中，有效项是项堆栈的可能顶部。那个，那个我们
could, that this item, could be the determination state of the
会不会，这个项目，会不会是
nondeterministic automaton. A simpler way of explaining the same idea is that for a
非确定性自动机。解释相同概念的一种更简单的方法是，对于
given viable prefix alpha the items that are valid in that prefix are exactly the
在给定可行前缀alpha的情况下，该前缀中有效的项恰好是
items that are in the final state of the DFA after it reads that prefix. So these
读取该前缀后处于DFA最终状态的项目。所以这些都是
are the items that describe the state after you've seen the stack alpha. Now, an
是在您看到堆栈alpha之后描述状态的项。现在，一个
item is often valid for many, many prefixes. So, for example, the item T goes
项通常对多个前缀有效。所以，举个例子，项目T是这样的
to open paren .e closed paren is valid for all sequences of open parens. And to see
要打开Paren，.E闭合Paren对所有左括号序列都有效。并且要看到
that, We can just look at our automaton and confirm that if we see an open paren,
我们只要看看我们的机器人就可以确认，如果我们看到一个张开的帕伦，
remember, this is the start state. So if we see an open paren, we take this
请记住，这是开始状态。所以如果我们看到一个敞开的帕伦，我们拿着这个
transition, we wind up in this state here. And then every open paren we see, we just
过渡的时候，我们就到了这个状态。然后我们看到的每一个开放的帕伦，我们只是
go round and round in this state. So if I have a sequence of five open parens as my
在这种状态下转来转去。所以如果我有一个由五个左括号组成的序列作为我的
input, then I'll have transitions one, two, three, four, five, all looping in
输入，然后我会有一个、二个、三个、四个、五个转换，所有这些都循环进入
this state. And notice that this item. Is, in, is one of the items in that state. And
这种状态。请注意这件物品。是，在，是处于那种状态的物品之一。和
that just says that this item is valid for any prefix, or for, excuse me, any
那就是说这个项目对任何前缀都有效，或者，对不起，对任何
sequence of open parens.
左括号的序列。